fusionbposervices.com 2012-06-14

# Fusion Privacy Policies

## Privacy Statement :- 

Fusion BPO Services is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Fusion BPO Services website and governs data collection and usage. By using the Fusion BPO Services website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information :**

Fusion BPO Services collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Fusion BPO Services also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Fusion BPO Services. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Fusion BPO Services for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Fusion BPO Services website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Fusion BPO Services public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Fusion BPO Services does not read any of your private online communications.

Fusion BPO Services encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Fusion BPO Services so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Fusion BPO Services is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Fusion BPO Services and Fusion BPO Services family of websites.

**Use of your Personal Information :**

Fusion BPO Services collects and uses your personal information to operate the Fusion BPO Services website and deliver the services you have requested. Fusion BPO Services also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Fusion BPO Services and its affiliates. Fusion BPO Services may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Fusion BPO Services does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Fusion BPO Services may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Fusion BPO Services may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Fusion BPO Services and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Fusion BPO Services does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Fusion BPO Services keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within Fusion BPO Services, in order to determine what Fusion BPO Services services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Fusion BPO Services to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Fusion BPO Services websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Fusion BPO Services or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Fusion BPO Services ; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Fusion BPO Services , or the public.

**Use of Cookies :**

The Fusion BPO Services website use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenient feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Fusion BPO Services pages, or register with Fusion BPO Services site or services, a cookie helps Fusion BPO Services to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Fusion BPO Services website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Fusion BPO Services features that you customized. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Fusion BPO Services services or websites you visit.

**Security of your Personal Information :**

Fusion BPO Services secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Fusion BPO Services secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Changes to this Statement :**

Fusion BPO Services will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Fusion BPO Services encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Fusion BPO Services is protecting your information.

**Contact Information :**

Fusion BPO Services welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Fusion BPO Services has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Fusion BPO Services at contact@fusionbposervices.com or the Office of Chief Privacy Officer directly. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem. 

**This policy was last modified on November 24, 2008**

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

**CHIEF PRIVACY OFFICER  
1111 St.Urbain  
Suite 200   
Montreal QC H2Z 1Y6  
ASAMANJA.CHATTERJEE@FUSIONBPOSERVICES.COM **
